mathplayground.com 2014-03-29

# Math Playground Privacy Statement

**Privacy and Information**

**Personal Information**  
MathPlayground.com does not collect any personal information from children. Nor do we collect personal information from anyone who visits this site. MathPlayground.com does **not** use any of the following solicitations when conducting business: 

\- mailing lists  
\- newsletters  
\- contests  
\- forms 

**Advertising**  
The ads appearing on this web site are delivered to you by our advertising partners. Information about your visit to this site, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to you on this site. Google ads are targeted specifically to the content within MathPlayground.com and we have taken numerous measures to help ensure that these ads link only to family friendly advertisers.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

**In response to the new COPPA rules, MathPlayground.com has opted out of behaviorally targeted ads from all of our advertising networks, and instead only shows contextually-based ads or other carefully-selected ads which are not based on a user's browsing behavior.** 

**Sponsors**  
We do provide links to third-party sites that sponsor Math Playground. These sites provide high quality educational content at a subscription rate. However, since we do not own or control these web sites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these (and all) third-party sites. MathPlayground.com does not share any information with these third party sites.  

**Terms of Use**

**Web Site Content**  
Multimedia content such as video lessons and interactive exercises are for online use only. These programs may not be downloaded, copied, reproduced, changed, or distributed in any way without the written permission of the publisher. 

**Submissions**  
Anything that is sent to MathPlayground.com by email, regular mail or submission forms on the web site is the exclusive property of the publisher. The publisher has the right to unrestricted use of these submissions for any purpose commercial or otherwise without compensation to the provider of the submissions.  

**Contacting MathPlayground.com**

All inquiries concerning MathPlayground.com and its policies may be sent to:

Colleen King  
colleen_king@mathplayground.com
